<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Where Am I</string>
    <string name="introduce_email">Enter your email address</string>
    <string name="introduce_password">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="dont_have">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="register_here">Register here</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="lower_letter">- Minimum one lower case letter</string>
    <string name="upper_letter">- Minimum one upper case letter</string>
    <string name="digit">- Minimum one digit</string>
    <string name="minimum_length">- Minimum 8 characters in length</string>
    <string name="password_requirements">Password requirements</string>
    <string name="registration_failed">Registration failed, check registration information</string>
    <string name="account_exists">Go Back and log in, your account exists</string>
    <string name="registration_successful">Registration complete, you will return to the login screen.</string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="enter">Start application</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="home_screen">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="items">Items</string>
    <string name="characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="trinkets">Trinkets</string>
    <string name="pickups">Pickups</string>
    <string name="about">About the game</string>
    <string name="plot">When Isaac’s mother starts hearing the voice of God demanding a sacrifice be made to prove her faith, Isaac escapes into the basement facing droves of deranged enemies, lost brothers and sisters, his fears, and eventually his mother.</string>
    <string name="gameplay">Gameplay</string>
    <string name="gameplay_text">The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth is a randomly generated action RPG shooter with heavy roguelike elements. Players will accompany Isaac on a quest to escape his mother, facing off against droves of mysterious creatures, discovering secrets, and fighting fearsome bosses. Along the way, Isaac can find bizarre treasures that change his form and give him super-human abilities. But it won\'t be easy!</string>
    <string name="important_information">Important information</string>
    <string name="information_character">There are 34 playable characters in The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth, each character  starts with different stats and abilities that give them their own unique playstyle.</string>
    <string name="information_item">Items are an integral part of the gameplay of The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth. They modify Isaac\'s attributes, grant or modify tear effects, and much more.</string>
    <string name="information_trinket">Trinkets are a kind of collectible with their designated slot that provide passive bonuses. Only one trinket can be carried at a time and must be dropped if you wish to carry another.</string>
    <string name="more_information">More information</string>
    <string name="attributes">Attributes</string>
    <string name="health_stat">Health: The amount of damage the character can take before dying.</string>
    <string name="healt">Health:</string>
    <string name="health">Health\n</string>
    <string name="speed_stat">Speed: How quickly the character moves.</string>
    <string name="tears_stat">Tears: The character\'s rate of fire. The higher the number, the faster tears are fired.</string>
    <string name="damage_stat">Damage: The amount of damage that each of the character\'s tears deals to enemies.</string>
    <string name="range_stat">Range: How long the character\'s tears will travel before landing.</string>
    <string name="shot_speed_stat">Shot Speed: How quickly the character\'s tears travel</string>
    <string name="luck_stat">Luck: Affects a variety of chance-based effects.</string>
    <string name="pickups_info">Pickups are minor items that can be found throughout the game.</string>
    <string name="chests_info">Chests are objects that contain other objects, items, trinkets, pickups, enemies, other chests, and more. There are eleven types of chests.</string>
    <string name="pills_info">Pills are pickups that can provide useful or inhibiting effects.At the start of each run, an effect is randomly assigned to each color of pill. The pill effect for each color will remain constant throughout the run.</string>
    <string name="cards_rune_info">Cards and runes are usable items with a wide variety of effects</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="item_details">Item details</string>
    <string name="effect">"Description: "</string>
    <string name="type">"Type: "</string>
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="charges">"Charges: "</string>
    <string name="unlimited">Unlimited</string>
</resources>